seizinglife.com 2013-03-09

# Seizing Life | Privacy Policy

## Information Collection and Use

The domain owner is the sole owner of the information collected on this domain. Other than via "cookies" and the analysis of server log files, we do not collect information from our users.

## Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties.

## Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. However, we do store aggregate data so that we provide outside sources with general traffic statistics from our website (for example, we may use aggregate information in a press release that states "traffic at this domain increased by 40% this week.")

## Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us here or email us at [info@seizinglife.com](mailto:info@seizinglife.com).

Our Mission. It may sound corny, but our mission is to help you. Finding time to do anything us use today is very difficult. We know this.

In order to give you a little more time for some of the more important things, we've compiled this site, listing reviews, news and views about some of the things you make have questions about, or are looking for information on.

We're trying to be a one shot guide on how thing, and how life, works, Browse around, and come back soon, as we try to post news things every week.
